photographymad.com 2014-02-13

# Privacy Policy | Photography Mad

_If you require any more information or have any questions about this privacy policy, please feel free tocontact me._

At PhotographyMad.com, the privacy of visitors is of extreme importance. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by PhotographyMad.com and how it is used.

##  Log Files

Like many other Web sites, PhotographyMad.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyse trends, administer the site, track users' movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

##  Cookies and Web Beacons

PhotographyMad.com does not use cookies or web beacons.

##  DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on PhotographyMad.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to PhotographyMad.com and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Some of PhotographyMad.com's advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. PhotographyMad.com's advertising partners include Google Adsense.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send the advertisements and links that appear on PhotographyMad.com directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalise the advertising content that you see.

PhotographyMad.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt out of certain practices. PhotographyMad.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
